so good afternoon
everyone i am adrika and uh
now it's finally time for our next
question
for our fourth question of day three
which in total will be our 14th question
so let's start with the question first
of all
so this is the question so
so you are driving and notice at 50
meter distance that in five seconds
the signal will turn red so what will
you do in this situation
you uh a drive fast as possible
drive as fast as possible is the option
a then we have b
stop and wait at the signal see
don't take any action d start honking
i'll once again repeat it
[Music]
all of us all of us are road users
and we all drive on road or we are a
pedestrian but we all are using roads
but still these roads they are not the
safest means of transport
and to make them the safest means of
transport the first thing that we should
know
is awareness that why do these accidents
happen
you know millions of us drive on indian
roads and 415 people
they die every day because of road
crashes
so what we can do is simple uh you know
like we have
our quiz contest here so uh this is like
one of the steps which we are taking
uh to free india from these road crashes
because just by answering such simple
questions
we can learn a lot so what all we can do
by answering these questions
the first is that we can learn a lot
we can save many lives of people who are
dying on indian roads every day
and what else we can do is if we
give the correct answer you can also win
some uh
you can also win some exclusive gifts uh
either a bike safety kit for you and
your family
or a car safety kit so
you know just with this simple step just
by answering this question
we can learn a lot we can save some
lives and also we can
uh we can uh get these uh
get these gifts so isn't so it's really
amazing that
how just by answering this
small question we become a part
you know uh just by answering this
little question we become a
part of making sure we become a part and
we
make sure that no more people die on
indian roads
anymore uh and the most important thing
is that you can also get these
uh gifts also so it's really nice to see
that
how we are benefited by just simply
answering
these questions so
uh what is the question so
uh so the question is that you are
driving
and you notice that at 50 right at about
meters distance uh
that at 50 meters distance that in five
seconds the signal will turn red
so what will you do in this situation a
drive as fast as possible b
stop and wait at the signal c
don't take any action b
[Music]
so so you know this is the question and
it is really simple to answer
every day we will be getting these
questions they are all related to road
safety uh
with this we come to know that how we
can save uh many
lives on indian roads uh because
uh just by this simple step just by
answering this question
we can also learn a lot so now how to
answer this question
it is really simple uh so
uh so first of all you can either
answer this question with the help of
the link
in the description uh with the help of
that link you can answer this question
or you can answer this from our youtube
page or from our
facebook page so you know these types of
questions you will be getting them
every day uh every day for two hours
each of these questions they are valid
uh they are valid for
two hours like we have this question it
will be valid for two hours
so with this we can learn a lot and it
is also really easy to participate
so just as i said that all of us you
know millions of us drive on indian
roads every day
and 415 people die because of road
crashes
and uh because of this increasing number
road crashes have become one of the uh
one of the biggest reasons of why
unnatural deaths are happening
in our country so to avoid that
to make sure that uh less
that that only few people die on these
roads uh this campaign is there and you
can know
from these small questions only that how
uh we can learn a lot that how we should
uh that how our behavior should be there
uh what we all can do uh you know
like our topic is road safety and all
the questions
uh we had and all the questions which we
will be getting
they're all related to road safety
because uh just by following these
simple steps
uh we can learn a lot you know like
once we will get the results uh and the
answers we can learn from these answers
like
uh many a times
[Music]
or why we are on roads many people
uh they like they do not follow uh
road safety rules they do not follow
traffic rules
like if we take a small example of
helmets
that people do not wear helmets it is
scene key
when people see traffic police then only
they wear helmets
so we must understand that not for
children but for our
own safety for the sake of our own life
we should be following these rules and
what we can do is
improve our behavior like each and every
question which we have
here which you will be answering and
you all have had answered so
so with these questions you we can learn
a lot and that is why you all can become
a part of this camping you all can
become a part
to make sure that no more people die on
these roads
the number of crashes they become less
and and peop and people understand that
why it is an important topic so
uh so you all can become a part with
this simple step and that is answering a
question
and you can also ask your family and
friends also to participate
like our each question is valid for two
hours
so so you can also tell
your friends your family about this and
ask them also to answer this
because they will also learn a lot uh by
simply answering these questions
and ask them uh to uh participate
in the next questions and i'll request
you
also all of you who are watching here uh
everyone should participate in the next
questions which will be coming
because with these uh small questions
we can we can just learn a lot
so i'll discuss the question once again
so you are driving and you notice
at 50 meters distance that in five
seconds
the signal will turn red you will
a drive as fast as possible
b stop and wait at the signal
c don't take any action d
start honking so
so uh you know for answering this
question
uh i'll request everyone to answer this
question at least try to answer this
question at the end when we will be
getting our
results then uh then
uh we can know that uh whatever behavior
should be like
and with answering these uh small
questions we can
uh learn a lot and you can also tell
about this to your family to your
friends
uh to make sure we'll be secret seeking
and they can also win a gift and you can
also win these prizes
so uh so either
uh you'll get a bike safety kit or
a car safety kit so you know
they this is really uh nice that
we can just learn a lot by simply
answering these small questions
so uh every two hours
we will be getting a new question like
if uh
like the uh like the fourth question of
today
uh the question which we are discussing
right now it is valid for two hours
so you can answer this question within
these two hours
uh and it's really simple to answer
either you can answer it with the link
in description
or from our youtube or facebook page
uh so and i'll request you all to also
answer the questions which will be
coming next the fifth
question uh which will be coming in next
two hours
[Music]
so the results of these questions
they will be announced at 10 pm every
day we have a show called bluntly
speaking
uh in that show the results will be
announced the winners will be announced
as well as the
correct answer of uh of these questions
it will also be announced uh and uh the
results
will also be there on our web page so
you can see it see the results from
anywhere either from our show called
bluntly speaking at 10 pm
uh it uh this show comes every day
at 10 pm either you can get your results
uh you can either check your results
from there uh and also from our
web page so i will request all of you to
please
be a part of this please be a
part to me uh part of this campaign to
make sure that
lesser people die on indian roads
uh you know our roads
uh right now they're really dangerous uh
you know
anytime any accident can happen and to
make these roads safer uh i will request
all of you to please be a part of this
and it is really simple you just have to
simply answer this
question i'm repeating in once again
so you are driving and you notice at 50
meters distance
that in five seconds the signal will
turn
red you will a
drive as fast as possible b
stop and wait at the signal c
don't take any action or d start honking
[Music]
so it is really simple to answer either
with the link
or from our facebook or youtube page the
results will be announced in our show
bluntly speaking which comes every day
so thank you so much everyone uh it was
really great
uh and i hope all of you will answer
this question
as well as the other questions uh also
so thank you everyone and please be a
part of this
uh and please tell everyone about this
to make sure that the that lesser people
die
on roads and our indian roads they
become
safer thank you
you